justfreestuff.com 2004-12-09

# Privacy Statement for Just Free Stuff

## Privacy Statement for Just Free Stuff

Just Free Stuff has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Just Free Stuff.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user promotional material from some of our partners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **Just Free Stuff** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.)

## Supplementation Information

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

## Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program. 

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [james@justfreestuff.com](mailto:james@justfreestuff.com)
  2. You can send a BLANK email to the following address: [mailto:justfreestuff-unsubscribe@topica.email-publisher.com](mailto:justfreestuff-unsubscribe@topica.email-publisher.com)  

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [james@justfreestuff.com](mailto:james@justfreestuff.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

James Barton  6351 W. Montrose #241  Chicago, IL. 60634-1563  c/o: Just Free Stuff  james@justfreestuff.com
